Okay. So there are elections taking place in a number of states today. Ohio, y'all have
abortion rights on the ballot. Kentucky, you have Daniel Cameron on the ballot, who is the attorney
general that did not indict the officers responsible for the unaliving of Breonna Taylor.
He is on the ballot as governor. There are a number of other states, including Mississippi,
that have voting today. I understand that there are some folks who think it is radical. They feel
it is rebellious to not make a choice around who is going to be in position of creating the laws
moving forward in your state. I see people doing things like writing in just something in the blank
spaces on the ballots. And I know that in some cases you are writing in things that you are
passionate about, that you believe in. I want to remind you, the individuals who you are not voting
against, but who you are essentially voting for, what they believe in is your oppression.
What they believe in is the power to indiscriminately determine the lives of the poor,
of women, of non-white people. And it is our responsibility to do everything we can to prevent
them. And that includes voting, even if the other candidate ain't that great.
A key element of responsibility is making a decision, even when it is a difficult one.